<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Erste Hilfe Kurs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53066/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Erste Hilfe Kurs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:53066/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Krankenschwester erzählt herzzerreißende Geschichte: „Dieses Anti-Erstickungs-Gerät hätte das Leben meines Sohnes retten können&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/lifevac-adv-l1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/lifevac-adv-l1/</guid>
      <description>Die weltweit vierthäufigste Ursache für einen Unfalltod ist Ersticken – und es kann Menschen jeden Alters treffen!&#xA;Vor zehn Jahren habe ich meinen jüngsten Sohn Noah durch einen plötzlichen, vermeidbaren Unfall verloren.&#xA;Es ist schwer, darüber zu schreiben, aber ich habe das Gefühl, dass ich es tun muss. Denn ich glaube, dass meine Geschichte jedem Menschen helfen wird, nicht dasselbe Schicksal zu erleben.&#xA;Am Ende dieses Artikels werden Sie GENAU wissen, wie Sie auf einen Erstickungsanfall reagieren müssen, sei es zu Hause, im Büro, in der Schule oder im Pflegeheim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notaufnahme-Schwester erzählt herzzerreißende Geschichte: Dieses Anti-Choking-Gerät hätte das Leben meines Sohnes retten können</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/lifevac-adv-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/lifevac-adv-1/</guid>
      <description>Ersticken ist weltweit die vierthäufigste Ursache für einen Unfalltod &amp;hellip; und es kann Menschen jeden Alters treffen!&#xA;Vor zehn Jahren habe ich meinen jüngsten Sohn Noah durch einen plötzlichen, vermeidbaren Unfall verloren.&#xA;Es ist schwer, darüber zu schreiben, aber ich habe das Gefühl, dass ich es tun muss. Denn** ich glaube, dass meine Geschichte Ihnen helfen kann, die gleiche Tragödie zu vermeiden.**&#xA;Am Ende dieses Artikels werden Sie GENAU wissen, wie Sie auf einen Erstickungsanfall reagieren müssen, sei es zu Hause, im Büro, in der Schule oder im Pflegeheim.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erstickungsgefahr bei Kindern: Was Eltern wissen sollten</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/posts/erstickungsgefahr-kinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/posts/erstickungsgefahr-kinder/</guid>
      <description>Erstickungsgefahr bei Kindern: Was Eltern wissen sollten Die unterschätzte Gefahr Viele Eltern sind sich nicht bewusst, dass alltägliche Snacks eine ernsthafte Erstickungsgefahr für ihre Kinder darstellen können. Produkte wie Bonbons, Nüsse, Chips, Trockenfrüchte, Popcorn und Kaugummis können leicht verschluckt werden und die Atemwege blockieren.&#xA;Besondere Risiken Weintrauben stellen beispielsweise ein hohes Risiko dar. Ihre glatte Oberfläche kann einen luftdichten Verschluss in der Speiseröhre bilden, was das Erstickungsrisiko erhöht. Schottische Wissenschaftler haben festgestellt, dass Weintrauben nach Würstchen und Süßigkeiten die dritthäufigste Ursache für Erstickungsunfälle bei Kindern sind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebensrettende Wirkung von LifeVac: Eine Mutter teilt ihre Erfahrung</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/posts/lifevac-erfolgstory-einer-mutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/posts/lifevac-erfolgstory-einer-mutter/</guid>
      <description>Lebensrettende Wirkung von LifeVac: Eine Mutter teilt ihre Erfahrung Bei LifeVac geht es nicht nur um ein Produkt, es geht um echte Lebensrettung. Dies wurde mir kürzlich durch eine bewegende Geschichte einer Mutter klar, deren 15-monatiger Sohn an einem Stück Brokkoli zu ersticken drohte.&#xA;Ein beängstigender Moment Der kleine Junge begann zu husten, als sich das Stück Brokkoli in seinem Hals festsetzte. Seine Mutter erkannte sofort, dass es sich um eine totale Verstopfung handelte, eine Situation, die jeder Elternteil fürchtet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LifeVac rettet Leben: Die Geschichte eines 44-jährigen Mannes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/posts/lifevac-erfolgstory-44-mann/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/posts/lifevac-erfolgstory-44-mann/</guid>
      <description>LifeVac rettet Leben: Die Geschichte eines 44-jährigen Mannes Heute teilen wir eine erstaunliche Geschichte, die die Bedeutung von LifeVac unterstreicht. Ein 44-jähriger Mann, der allein zu Hause war, erlitt eine vollständige Atemwegsblockade, als er an einem Stück Sesamhuhn zu ersticken begann.&#xA;Ein unerwarteter Vorfall Er war gerade dabei, sich zwischen E-Mails und Videokonferenzen schnell etwas zu Essen zu machen, als der Vorfall eintrat. Seine Freundin war kurz weg, und er stand alleine der lebensbedrohlichen Situation gegenüber.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wartezeiten auf Rettungswagen in Deutschland: Ein Überblick</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/posts/rettungswagen-wartezeiten/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/posts/rettungswagen-wartezeiten/</guid>
      <description>Wartezeiten auf Rettungswagen in Deutschland: Ein Überblick Die durchschnittliche Wartezeit In Deutschland dauert es im Durchschnitt 12 bis 15 Minuten, bis ein Rettungswagen am Einsatzort eintrifft. Diese Zeiten variieren jedoch je nach Bundesland und den dort geltenden Vorgaben. In Sachsen, Nordrhein-Westfalen, Saarland und Sachsen-Anhalt beispielsweise sollen 95% der Notrufe innerhalb von maximal 12 Minuten erreicht werden. In Mecklenburg-Vorpommern sind es 10 Minuten und in Niedersachsen bis zu 15 Minuten.&#xA;Regionale Unterschiede Es gibt erhebliche regionale Unterschiede.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meine Erfahrungen mit LifeVac - Ein Lebensretter in Notsituationen</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/posts/lifevac-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 14:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/posts/lifevac-review/</guid>
      <description>Einleitung Im heutigen Beitrag möchte ich meine Erfahrungen mit einem innovativen Produkt teilen, das das Potenzial hat, Leben zu retten: LifeVac. LifeVac ist ein Gerät zur Entfernung von Atemwegsobstruktionen, das speziell entwickelt wurde, um im Notfall schnell und effektiv zu helfen.&#xA;Hintergrund LifeVac ist ein nicht-invasives, tragbares Absauggerät, das entwickelt wurde, um bei Erstickungsnotfällen zu helfen, wenn herkömmliche Methoden wie Schläge auf den Rücken oder der Heimlich-Griff versagen. Sein einfaches Design macht es leicht zu benutzen, auch für Menschen ohne medizinische Vorkenntnisse.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This New Gadget Eases My Headaches In Seconds (and it’s completely natural)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/theraice/featured/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 14:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/theraice/featured/</guid>
      <description>If you struggle with headaches or migraines on a regular basis, read closely – this story could change your life! My headaches started in my early 40s. Of course, I’d had headaches before – but when they began happening daily, I started to freak out.&#xA;I assumed it was stress at first… but the pain simply didn’t stop. In fact, it got worse.&#xA;Eventually, my headaches felt like they were in control of my entire life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Strange “Headache Relief Cap” Eliminates My Headaches In Seconds (It’s Like A Spa Treatment At Home)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/theraice/featured-bu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 14:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/theraice/featured-bu/</guid>
      <description>If you struggle with headaches or migraines on a regular basis, read closely – this story could change your life! My headaches started in my early 40s. Of course, I’d had headaches before – but when they began happening daily, I started to freak out.&#xA;I assumed it was stress at first… but the pain simply didn’t stop. In fact, it got worse.&#xA;Eventually, my headaches felt like they were in control of my entire life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Strange “Headache Relief Cap” Eliminates My Headaches In Seconds (It’s Like A Spa Treatment At Home)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/theraice/theraice-en/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 14:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/theraice/theraice-en/</guid>
      <description>If you struggle with headaches or migraines on a regular basis, read closely – this story could change your life! My headaches started in my early 40s. Of course, I’d had headaches before – but when they began happening daily, I started to freak out.&#xA;I assumed it was stress at first… but the pain simply didn’t stop. In fact, it got worse.&#xA;Eventually, my headaches felt like they were in control of my entire life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This New Gadget Ease Headaches In Seconds (and it’s completely natural)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/theraice/theraice-en-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/theraice/theraice-en-2/</guid>
      <description>If you struggle with headaches or migraines on a regular basis, read closely – this story could change your life! My headaches started in my early 40s. Of course, I’d had headaches before – but when they began happening daily, I started to freak out.&#xA;I assumed it was stress at first… but the pain simply didn’t stop. In fact, it got worse.&#xA;Eventually, my headaches felt like they were in control of my entire life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Datenschutz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/datenschutz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/datenschutz/</guid>
      <description>Wir möchten Sie nachfolgend über die Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten im Rahmen der Nutzung unserer Internetseiten informieren.&#xA;Welche Daten werden verarbeitet? Rechtsgrundlagen der Datenverarbeitung Um Ihnen unsere Internetseite und die damit verbundenen Dienstleistungen anbieten zu können, verarbeiten wir personenbezogene Daten auf Basis folgender Rechtsgrundlagen:&#xA;Einwilligung (Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. a) DSGVO) zur Erfüllung von Verträgen (Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. b) DSGVO auf Basis einer Interessenabwägung (Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer for GadgetAdvisers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>If you require any more information or have any questions about our site’s disclaimer, please feel free to contact us by email at disclaimer@gadgetadvisers.com&#xA;Disclaimers for GadgetAdvisers All the information on this website – https://GadgetAdvisers.org/ – is published in good faith and for general information purpose only. GadgetAdvisers does not make any warranties about the completeness, reliability and accuracy of this information. Any action you take upon the information you find on this website (GadgetAdvisers), is strictly at your own risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impressum GadgetAdvisers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG ROAS Performance Marketing Limited&#xA;Ebene Mews, 57 Plaines Wilhems Cybercity, Ebene 72201 Republic of Mauritius&#xA;Place of registration: Corporate and Business Registration, Department at Port Louis, Mauritius Business Registration Number: 175888&#xA;Kontakt E-Mail: info@gadgetadvisers.com Website: www.gadgetadvisers.com&#xA;Verbraucherstreitbeilegung/ Universalschlichtungsstelle Wir sind nicht bereit oder verpflichtet, an Streitbeilegungsverfahren vor einer Verbraucherschlichtungsstelle teilzunehmen.&#xA;Haftung für Inhalte Als Diensteanbieter sind wir gemäß § 7 Abs.1 TMG für eigene Inhalte auf diesen Seiten nach den allgemeinen Gesetzen verantwortlich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy for GadgetAdvisers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy for GadgetAdvisers At GadgetAdvisers, accessible from https://GadgetAdvisers.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by GadgetAdvisers and how we use it.&#xA;If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.&#xA;Log Files GadgetAdvisers follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xD;LifeVac | The Life-Saving Device&#xD;LifeVac 10 Year Celebration - Press Release&#xA;Advertorial&#xA;Buy 2 + Get 1 Free Evidence Based&#xD;Expert Reviewed&#xD;This Revolutionary New Doctor-Approved Device Can Save You From Choking In Seconds&#xA;Posted By Jeremey W&#xA;Published On Wed, Sep 14&#xA;Reading Time 4 Minutes&#xA;If a loved one starts choking, you don’t have to think about anything… the LifeVac does all the work. And it’s 100% effective to date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xD;LifeVac | The Life-Saving Device Advertorial&#xD;Trending&#xD;New Anti-Choking Device Can Save Your Child&#39;s Life... No Training Needed&#xD;Sponsored by LifeVac&#xD;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/lifevac/3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xD;LifeVac | The Life-Saving Device Advertorial&#xA;This Revolutionary New Doctor-Approved Device Can Save You From Choking In Seconds&#xD;Sponsored by LifeVac&#xD;“If a loved one starts choking, you don’t have to think about anything… the LifeVac does all the work. And it’s 100% effective to date…”&#xA;I remember it like yesterday. My 13-month-old son Elliott was sitting in his high chair, eating flat pretzels like he had a million times before…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/theraice/thera-ice-headache-relief-hat-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/theraice/thera-ice-headache-relief-hat-de/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, welcome to our website!&#xA;Gadget Advisers pop up from some geeky friends, including engineers and tech enthusiasts who have always loved reading and researching all the new technologies and gadgets online.&#xA;Our passion for discovering new objects that can help us around the house grows more and more every year. We joke all the time about how we are that friend or nephew or cousin who helps when people have tech problems, or when they find something new online to buy, but are concerned about the quality and provenance of the products.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/contact/</guid>
      <description>Do you need help or would you like to praise or criticize? Fill out the form, our team is looking forward to hearing from you.&#xA;Do you want to be our partner? We strive for trustful cooperation with our customers, first of all to ensure their full satisfaction. If you have a product and service that fits our profile and would like to advertise on gadgetadvisers.com, please contact us, we look forward to talking to you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gadget Ambassador Programm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/gadget-ambassador/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/gadget-ambassador/</guid>
      <description>Do you love gadgets like we do? Join our Gadget Ambassador Program and get access to our exclusive Facebook Group and test amazing gadgets as one of the firsts.&#xA;Benefits Free products, commission earning potential, giveaways, access to events and more.&#xA;Sign up Sign up for our Gadget Ambassador Program with this link.&#xA;Share content Get rewards FAQs: How old I need to be? Minumum 18 years.&#xA;Gadget Ambassadors by GadgetAdvisors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good bye!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/no-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/no-ads/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been successfully unsubscribed from our ads. If you change your mind click here:&#xA;This feature only works if you allowed Facebook Targeting, otherwise there is no way to exclude you from our ads.&#xA;If you want to help us improve we would like to get feedback. form</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/partner/</guid>
      <description>Do you have products? We are happy to hear about your products. Fill out the form and we are getting in contact with you soon.&#xA;Click here to contact us.&#xA;Do you want to become an ambassador? If you love gadgets like we do and want to be part of Gadgeradvisors.&#xA;Click here to learn more.&#xA;Click here to apply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Share Feedback</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/share-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/share-feedback/</guid>
      <description>We offer $25 Coupon of your choice for</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/about-us/</guid>
      <description>A paragraph looks like this — dolor amet cray stumptown fingerstache neutra food truck seitan poke cardigan waistcoat VHS snackwave celiac hella. Godard seitan shoreditch flexitarian next level trust fund man braid vegan listicle keytar bitters. Disrupt cray fashion axe unicorn lomo shaman poke glossier keffiyeh snackwave austin tattooed seitan hexagon lo-fi. Lumbersexual irony vaporware, butcher shaman.&#xA;Headings by default: H1 Default styles for headings H2 Default styles for headings H3 Default styles for headings H4 Default styles for headings H5 Default styles for headings H6 Default styles for headings Lists Ordered list example: Poutine drinking vinegar bitters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>A paragraph looks like this — dolor amet cray stumptown fingerstache neutra food truck seitan poke cardigan waistcoat VHS snackwave celiac hella. Godard seitan shoreditch flexitarian next level trust fund man braid vegan listicle keytar bitters. Disrupt cray fashion axe unicorn lomo shaman poke glossier keffiyeh snackwave austin tattooed seitan hexagon lo-fi. Lumbersexual irony vaporware, butcher shaman.&#xA;Headings by default: H1 Default styles for headings H2 Default styles for headings H3 Default styles for headings H4 Default styles for headings H5 Default styles for headings H6 Default styles for headings Lists Ordered list example: Poutine drinking vinegar bitters.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
