<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Erste Hilfe Kurs</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53066/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Erste Hilfe Kurs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:53066/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Datenschutz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/datenschutz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/datenschutz/</guid>
      <description>Wir möchten Sie nachfolgend über die Verarbeitung personenbezogener Daten im Rahmen der Nutzung unserer Internetseiten informieren.&#xA;Welche Daten werden verarbeitet? Rechtsgrundlagen der Datenverarbeitung Um Ihnen unsere Internetseite und die damit verbundenen Dienstleistungen anbieten zu können, verarbeiten wir personenbezogene Daten auf Basis folgender Rechtsgrundlagen:&#xA;Einwilligung (Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. a) DSGVO) zur Erfüllung von Verträgen (Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit. b) DSGVO auf Basis einer Interessenabwägung (Art. 6 Abs. 1 lit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclaimer for GadgetAdvisers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>If you require any more information or have any questions about our site’s disclaimer, please feel free to contact us by email at disclaimer@gadgetadvisers.com&#xA;Disclaimers for GadgetAdvisers All the information on this website – https://GadgetAdvisers.org/ – is published in good faith and for general information purpose only. GadgetAdvisers does not make any warranties about the completeness, reliability and accuracy of this information. Any action you take upon the information you find on this website (GadgetAdvisers), is strictly at your own risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impressum GadgetAdvisers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/impressum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/impressum/</guid>
      <description>Angaben gemäß § 5 TMG ROAS Performance Marketing Limited&#xA;Ebene Mews, 57 Plaines Wilhems Cybercity, Ebene 72201 Republic of Mauritius&#xA;Place of registration: Corporate and Business Registration, Department at Port Louis, Mauritius Business Registration Number: 175888&#xA;Kontakt E-Mail: info@gadgetadvisers.com Website: www.gadgetadvisers.com&#xA;Verbraucherstreitbeilegung/ Universalschlichtungsstelle Wir sind nicht bereit oder verpflichtet, an Streitbeilegungsverfahren vor einer Verbraucherschlichtungsstelle teilzunehmen.&#xA;Haftung für Inhalte Als Diensteanbieter sind wir gemäß § 7 Abs.1 TMG für eigene Inhalte auf diesen Seiten nach den allgemeinen Gesetzen verantwortlich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy for GadgetAdvisers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy for GadgetAdvisers At GadgetAdvisers, accessible from https://GadgetAdvisers.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by GadgetAdvisers and how we use it.&#xA;If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.&#xA;Log Files GadgetAdvisers follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/about-us/</guid>
      <description>A paragraph looks like this — dolor amet cray stumptown fingerstache neutra food truck seitan poke cardigan waistcoat VHS snackwave celiac hella. Godard seitan shoreditch flexitarian next level trust fund man braid vegan listicle keytar bitters. Disrupt cray fashion axe unicorn lomo shaman poke glossier keffiyeh snackwave austin tattooed seitan hexagon lo-fi. Lumbersexual irony vaporware, butcher shaman.&#xA;Headings by default: H1 Default styles for headings H2 Default styles for headings H3 Default styles for headings H4 Default styles for headings H5 Default styles for headings H6 Default styles for headings Lists Ordered list example: Poutine drinking vinegar bitters.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:53066/page/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:53066/page/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>A paragraph looks like this — dolor amet cray stumptown fingerstache neutra food truck seitan poke cardigan waistcoat VHS snackwave celiac hella. Godard seitan shoreditch flexitarian next level trust fund man braid vegan listicle keytar bitters. Disrupt cray fashion axe unicorn lomo shaman poke glossier keffiyeh snackwave austin tattooed seitan hexagon lo-fi. Lumbersexual irony vaporware, butcher shaman.&#xA;Headings by default: H1 Default styles for headings H2 Default styles for headings H3 Default styles for headings H4 Default styles for headings H5 Default styles for headings H6 Default styles for headings Lists Ordered list example: Poutine drinking vinegar bitters.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
